bellacor.com 2012-05-08

# Privacy Policy | BELLACOR.COM’S Commitment To Privacy

   PRIVACY POLICY   
---  
  
Commitment to Privacy  
Bellacor.com is concerned about your privacy and the security of your personal data. We have made a strong effort to ensure that your personal information is safeguarded. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used. It discloses the privacy guidelines for Bellacor.com, Inc. websites: www.bellacor.com and www.bellacorpro.com. This notice is available on our homepage and on pages where personally identifiable information is requested.   
top | 

Commitment to  
    Privacy  
Collected Information  
Use of Information  
E–Mail  
Third Party Policy  
Commitment to Data  
    Security  
Electronic Security  

Cookies  

Collected Information  
In a few areas on our Web site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit or to follow up with you after your visit. It is optional for you to participate.   
We receive information from you when you: 

  1. Place an order 
  2. Subscribe to regularly scheduled e-mails 
  3. Sign up for one of our services 
  4. Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer 
  5. Provide feedback in an e-mail 

We may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer number, credit card number and expiration date. We may also request personal preference information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers, or make product recommendations. 

We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: o 

  * Fulfilling orders
  * Delivering packages
  * Sending Bellacor marketing communications
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Processing credit card payments
  * Providing chat functions

top | 

Encryption  
Commitment to  
    Children's Privacy  
Contact Us  

During Customer Support Hours  
Mon–Fri, 7 AM - 7 PM CT  
Sat, 8 AM - 4 PM; Sun, 9 AM - 5 PM 

Phone: 1-877-723-5522  
Email: [Customer Support](javascript:bellacorPopUp\('http://www.bellacor.com/contactUs.cfm?subject=Other', '645', '550', '1', '1', '0', '0'\))  

Use of Information  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell it to others.  
Name, address, phone number, customer number, and credit card information are used to ship and bill orders and for future marketing purposes. In addition, phone number and customer number are used in case there is a problem with your order and customer service needs to contact you. Personal information allows our websites to make product recommendations to you. If you provide us with your e-mail address, you may receive periodic e-mail promotions and special offers. 

We also gather data on visitor's movements through our sites. This information is used to improve our service to you and to administer our websites. Data on visitors' home servers is aggregated for internal review. The aggregate information on what pages are visited is used to improve the site content and also for error tracking purposes related to the functioning of the site. Individually identifiable e-mail addresses are not captured or stored for future use, unless you choose to communicate with Bellacor.com, Inc. by posting a message to Bellacor.com, Inc. 

Bellacor.com, Inc. may share information with subsidiaries and affiliates. If you do not want your information shared, simply e-mail [Customer Service](javascript:bellacorPopUp\('http://www.bellacor.com/contactUs.cfm?subject=Other', '645', '550', '1', '1', '0', '0'\)) (type "Do not share with affiliates" in the body of the message) or send a letter stating this preference to: 

Bellacor.com, Inc. Customer Service  
2425 Enterprise Drive, Suite 900  
Mendota Heights, MN 55120 

In any communication, be sure to include your name, mailing address, and customer account number.   
Persons who communicate with Bellacor.com, Inc. and therefore supply Bellacor.com, Inc. with an e-mail address may receive future communications from us by e-mail. You can unsubscribe at any time by e-mailing your request to [Customer Service](javascript:bellacorPopUp\('http://www.bellacor.com/contactUs.cfm?subject=Other', '645', '550', '1', '1', '0', '0'\)). Simply state, "Do not email" in the body of the message. Finally, please note that we also offer links to other third party sites and services. Be aware that these outside parties operate under their own privacy and security policies, and Bellacor.com, Inc. has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. All internal/external Bellacor.com, Inc. parties, such as employees, agents, and contractors are similarly bound by these privacy and security policies.   
top

|     
  
E–Mail  
If you provide Bellacor with your e–mail address, you may receive e–mails from us. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional e–mails from Bellacor, please [click here](http://www.bellacor.com/unsubscribe1.cfm). You may still receive e–mails from us if you have requested them through one of our site services such as Personal Shopper, Price Quote or Product Specialist.   
top|   
  
Third Party Policy  
Third Party Marketing is defined as a company that has no direct relationship with Bellacor.com, Inc. customers. Third parties will not contact you as a result of your subscribing to our e-mail newsletter and promotions lists except through advertisements within the newsletters themselves. 

We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).   
top

|   
  
Commitment to Data Security  
Bellacor.com, Inc. is committed to the security of information collected on our sites. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
top  
  
Electronic Security  
Private account information is located behind a firewall; it is not directly connected to the Internet. Information behind the firewall on the customer server is not available to unauthorized computers. The firewall is a recognized industry standard.   
top  
  
Cookies  
At Bellacor.com, Inc., we may use cookies to help us provide you with a fast, convenient shopping experience at our online store. A cookie is a data element a website sends to your browser. It is stored on your computer hard drive and tells a website that a previous visitor has returned. It doesn't automatically give personal information about you, like your e-mail address or name. 

If you want to give us personal information through registration, then a cookie will help us deliver content based on your interests and preferences. Cookies also help us monitor whether our websites are functioning properly and to perform site traffic analysis.   
top  

Encryption  
Encryption is a process by which we use software to scramble sensitive information while it is in transit to Bellacor.com, Inc. We use Secure Socket Layering (SSL). SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. It is based on a key that has two different parts: public and private. 

The public part of the key is distributed to those you want to communicate with. The private part is for recipients' use only. When you send personal information to us, you use our public key to encrypt your personal information. That means if your information is intercepted during the transmission, it is scrambled and very difficult to decrypt. Once we receive your encrypted personal information, we use the private part of our key to decode it. 

Making a credit card purchase online at Bellacor.com, Inc. is just as safe as making a credit card purchase over the telephone. However, if you would prefer to use the phone, just call 1-877-723-5522, and one of our product specialists will gladly take your order (8 am - 5 pm CT, Monday - Friday).   
top  

Commitment to Children's Privacy  
Protecting the online privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Bellacor.com, Inc. voluntarily complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and the US Federal Trade Commission's Children's Online Privacy Protection Rule. (16 C.F.R. Part 312). We neither collect nor maintain information at our site from those actually known to be under the age of 13, nor is any part of our sites directed to children under the age of 13.   
top  
  
Contact Us  
For additional information about our privacy policy and information maintained about you, please contact us at the following addresses. In any communication, be sure to include your name, mailing address, and customer account number. 

  * E-mail: [Customer Service](javascript:bellacorPopUp\('http://www.bellacor.com/contactUs.cfm', '645', '550', '1', '1', '0', '0'\))
  * Call: 1-877-723-5522
  * Mail: 2425 Enterprise Drive, Suite 900   
         Mendota Heights, MN 55120

Did this help? Continue Shopping   
Still have questions? Contact Us   
top
